

KONTAKT

Rzeszów, Poland



nastaluciv@gmail.com



+48 791 403 667



https://www.linkedin.com/in/an astasiia-lutsiv/



https://github.com/ltsvn



https://ltsvn.github.io/portfolio-React/

UMIEJĘTNOŚCI

- JavaScript
- **TypeScript**
- React
- Next.is
- Tailwind
- Redux
- · Redux Toolkit
- Redux Thunk
- Axins
- · React hooks
- Rest API
- GitLab
- MUIT
- Shadcn
- Postman
- Yup
- Storybook
- Bootstrap
- Shopify
- Liauid
- Webflow

EDUCATION

University of Information Tech. And Management

Business Intelligence in Management - Masters deg. | 10.2022 - 07.2024

University of Information Tech. And Management

Psychology in Management -Bachelors deg. | 10.2019 - 07.2022

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian - native English - B1 Polish - B2

ANASTASIIA LUTSIV

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Front-End developer with experience in creating SPAs using React, Next.js, and TypeScript. I'm always looking forward to improving my knowledge. In my free time, I also take on freelance projects, delivering complete solutions with a focus on web development, SEO optimization, and design. Outside of work, I enjoy improving my English, going to the gym, reading educational books, or solving katas on Codewars. I'm open to your suggestions!

WORK HISTORY

Front-End Developer

IT Spark, Rzeszów | 02.2024 - now

Responsibilities:

- End-to-end e-commerce project development: involvement in creating e-commerce projects from the initial concept stage to the final implementation.
- Collaboration within a development team: Working collaboratively with other developers and UX/UI specialists to develop and implement functionalities.
- Building components using React: Utilizing the React library to create components, manage component state, handle component lifecycle, and apply a reactive approach to interface development.
- Active participation in team meetings: Contributing ideas and suggestions during team meetings, sharing knowledge and experiences.

Front-End Intern

OPGK Software, Rzeszów | 09.2023 - 11.2023

Responsibilities:

- · Creating a first configuration creator for a dashboard from start to finish.
- Participation in writing a new project in React based on the
- Working in a development team, collaborating with UX/UI designers and other developers to develop and implement functionalities.
- Creating components using the React library, utilizing component state, component lifecycle, and a reactive approach to interface development.
- Designing graphical user interfaces to improve user experience.
- · Contributing ideas and suggestions in team meetings.

Project:

Mint Service Desk

• (technology using: react, typescript, react-hook-form, antd, yup, storybook)

Front-end Developer Trainee

IT-Incubator | 09.2022 - 08.2023

Responsibilities:

- Project architectural solutions (layering UI, BLL, DAL, Server);
- Proper BLL state management with Redux, Thunk Toolkit etc.;
- Working with the server using ajax (CRUD determination and data processing);
- Performance enhancement (memo, useCallback etc.);
- Covering applications with tests;
- Refactoring, bugs fixing, deploying;

Projects:

Social Network

 (technology using: react, redux, typescript, formik, mui, rest api, axios)

ToDo List

 (technology using: react, redux, typescript, formik, mui, rest api, axios)

Other projects you can see in my https://github.com/ltsvn.

HR IT Recruiter

OPGK Software, Rzeszów | 11.2021 - 08.2022

Responsibilities:

- Recruitment Planning
- Candidate Sourcing
- · Screening and Assessment
- Interviewing
- Candidate Engagement
- Employer Branding
- Collaboration and Coordination
- · Offer Negotiation
- Data Management
- Market Research

Junior Recruitment Specialist

Grupa Progres, Rzeszów | 03.2021 - 08.2021

Responsibilities:

- · Candidate Sourcing
- · Candidate Screening
- Job Matching
- Candidate Support
- Database Management
- Market Research
- Administrative Tasks

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).